<Document>
#Series 1 Combat Mechs

  The cheapest and most frequently deployed Mechs, most often utilized as a suit of Powered Armor for infantry conflicts and boarding actions.

  All S1 Mechs are space insulated, provide breathable atmosphere, and have maneuvering jets.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MechGygax"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MechDurand"/>
  </Box>

##Gygax

The Gygax is a fast, lightly-armored strike platform. It is vulnerable to handheld weaponry, but provides its operator protection from common combat injuries.

##Durand

The Durand is a slow, lumbering, heavily armored tank. It is vulnerable to concentrated fire but is durable enough to walk off injuries that would disable or destroy a Gygax.

##Weaponry
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatUltraRifle"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatShotgun" Caption="LBX AC-10"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatShotgunIncendiary"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatMissileRack8"/>
  </Box>
 - The Ultra AC-2 is a highly accurate light machine gun.
 - The LBX AC-10 is a light automatic shotgun that fires standard 12-guage buckshot.
 - The FNX-99 Hades Carbine is a light automatic shotgun that fires 12-gauge incendiary shells.
 - The SRM-8 Light Missile Rack is a self-loading unguided rocket launcher useful for breaching airlock doors.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatDisabler"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatFlashbangLauncher"/>
  </Box>
  - The CH-PD Disabler is a mech-mounted varient of the standard handheld Disabler.
  - The SGL-6 Flashbang Launcher does exactly what you would expect, for a surprisingly low cost.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatFiredartLaser"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatSolarisLaser"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponMechCombatImmolationGun"/>
  </Box>
  - The CH-PS Firedart is the mech-mounted equivalent to a Makeshift Laser Pistol.
  - The CH-LC Solaris is equivalent to a standard Laser Rifle.
  - The ZFI Immolation Beam Gun is equivalent to a Laser Cannon.


##Syndicate Mechs

The [color=crimson]Syndicate[/color] created variations of the standard powered armor Mechs which were provided to Nuclear Operatives in their station-destroying operations. These can still rarely be found deployed in the Colossus Sector.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MechGygaxSyndie"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MechMaulerSyndie"/>
  </Box>

  These mechs are invariably better than the standard-issue versions, featuring significant improvements to armor plating and an expanded equipment capacity.

</Document>
